Kavya Reddy

UI/UX Designer

9742901815

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Enthusiastic UX Designer with problem solving mindset and bringing robust experience in gathering and translating user data into design decisions. Coming to enhance the functionality and usability of platforms by developing user persona for target audience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer

Tata Consultancy Services 2020-Current

Analyst

Tata Consultancy Services

2019-2020

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information science Engineering

CMRIT Bangalore

2015 - 2019 | GPA: 7.98

PROJECTS

Visitor Management App for Hospital

Conducted interviews and created research reports.

Developed high-fidelity wireframes, clickable prototypes

Invo - Bill Payment Application

Conducted interviews and ideated based on insights. Designed high-fidelity wireframes, clickable prototypes and conducted usability testing.

NutriC - Nutrition Tracker Application

Empathized with users and created persona. Wireframes and low fidelity designs. Conducted AB usability testing. Created high fidelity designs and clickable prototypes.

Pre-hire Assessment & interview Application

Web application for candidates to take remote interviews and pre-hire assessments. conducted research and found insights. Created Style guide for consistent design, High Fidelity Prototype.

SKILLS & TOOLS

Skills

User Research
Wireframing & Protoyping
Interaction design
Decision Making
Interpersonal Skills
User Empathy
HTML & CSS

Tools

Figma

Adobe XD

Zeplin

Miro board

Balsamia Wireframes

Framer

CERTIFICATION

Google ux design professional certificate

coursera.org